<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[the 5amcrook]]></title><description><![CDATA[daily news to crook you up]]></description><link>https://5amcrook.netlify.app</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 18:14:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[WFH with a Nintendo Switch]]></title><description><![CDATA[In the current Work-from-Home economy, many people own Nintendo switches. How do they navigate the demands of actual work and the full-time job of being Resident Representative on their islands?]]></description><link>https://5amcrook.netlify.app/posts/wfh-acnh</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://5amcrook.netlify.app/posts/wfh-acnh</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;On 20th March 2020, Nintendo launched a new game from the Animal Crossing series. This game is none other than Animal Crossing: New Horizons. You must seen it somewhere, right? (Else you wouldn’t be here).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game is popular among kids, college students, and even working adults. While there is really nothing much to do in the game, there is also too much you can do in the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An interviewee, smolcano, shared her work-from-home setup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s imperative to have the switch placed right in front of my homework. That way, I can always be alert when a balloon flies by.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, balloons in ACNH are not the latex inflatables you see at parties. Every one will run after a balloon they see, even climbing up cliffs and crossing rivers. Yes, all that just so they can wring a slingshot at that balloon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;smolcano’s switch-work setup is not unique, which is no wonder the average playtime in the global player base is at least 12 hours a day.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>